[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "A fruit that keeps the doctor away if eaten daily",
        "answer": "apple"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "A fruit that is yellow and is a good source of potassium",
        "answer": "banana"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "A fruit that is red and is a good source of vitamin C",
        "answer": "strawberry"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "A fruit that is green and is a good source of vitamin K",
        "answer": "kiwi"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "A fruit that is orange and is a good source of vitamin A",
        "answer": "carrot"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "A fruit that is purple and is a good source of vitamin B6",
        "answer": "grape"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "A fruit that is brown and is a good source of vitamin E",
        "answer": "avocado"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "A fruit that is white and is a good source of vitamin B9",
        "answer": "banana"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "A fruit that is black and is a good source of vitamin B12",
        "answer": "blackberry"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "A fruit that is pink and is a good source of vitamin B1",
        "answer": "watermelon"
    }
]